<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd"
  xmlns:trackback="http://madskills.com/public/xml/rss/module/trackback/">
  <channel>
    <title>Fasparo</title>
    <link>http://fasparo.com</link>
    <description>Fasparo</description>
    <copyright>Fasparo</copyright>
    <pubDate>Sat, 19 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Data nirvana</title>
      <link>http://fasparo.com/blog/data-nirvana</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A personal computer is firstly a tool, but it was also intended to be place to store personal data. In 2015 most people have given up and entrusted all this stuff to corporate clouds. But I have doubled down and decided that my personal data (or at least the canonical version of it) belongs in a personal place, not in a data center. And after a decade or so on Linux, I have arrived at what feels like the ideal way to do that.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://fasparo.com/blog/data-nirvana</guid>
      <dc:date>2015-12-19T00:00:00+01:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bulletproof archiving</title>
      <link>http://fasparo.com/blog/bulletproof-archiving</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As part of my strategy for archiving important data, I have long had an &amp;quot;Archive&amp;quot; directory which I consider as a virtual safe-deposit box. That is: once inside, files can be consulted but not modified. The way to do this is by write-protecting them. Important documents and photos may then be freely opened in, say, a graphics program or a text editor without the risk of being overwritten inadvertently. But how can the write-protection be automated? With &lt;code&gt;inotifywait&lt;/code&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://fasparo.com/blog/bulletproof-archiving</guid>
      <dc:date>2015-11-22T00:00:00+01:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An alternative to independence</title>
      <link>http://fasparo.com/blog/independence-alternative</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It seems that whenever I visit Barcelona there are Catalan flags hanging from every window. The most recent time it was because of a pseudo-referendum on independence for Catalonia (which was only pseudo-won). Scotland and Quebec have each had multiple real referendums. Apparently all three countries will keep voting every decade or two until one day, maybe, the answer is Yes.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://fasparo.com/blog/independence-alternative</guid>
      <dc:date>2015-10-24T00:00:00+02:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A single relevant news feed</title>
      <link>http://fasparo.com/blog/single-relevant-feed</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;To follow people on Twitter as a means of finding news is to get an edited news feed in return for delegating to others your choice of sources. Alternatively, subscribing directly to news producers by RSS is to get a firehose in return for the privilege of choosing your own sources. In the first case you control the filter but not the source, in the second the source but not the filter.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://fasparo.com/blog/single-relevant-feed</guid>
      <dc:date>2015-09-11T00:00:00+02:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data hoarding</title>
      <link>http://fasparo.com/blog/data-hoarding</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It seems to be a human instinct to want to build personal collections of other people&amp;#39;s data.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://fasparo.com/blog/data-hoarding</guid>
      <dc:date>2015-08-21T00:00:00+02:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dismantling Babel</title>
      <link>http://fasparo.com/blog/linguistic-diversity</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Language is the biodiversity of the human species. And just as there will be fewer species of butterfly tomorrow than there are today, there will be fewer languages. From 7000 to 700 by the end of the century, by one estimate.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://fasparo.com/blog/linguistic-diversity</guid>
      <dc:date>2015-07-26T00:00:00+02:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delete the social button</title>
      <link>http://fasparo.com/blog/antisocial-button</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Social buttons do not belong on webpages. They are ugly, slow, a pain for developers to maintain, and in theory superfluous. Sharing, liking, tweeting, annotating, upvoting and downvoting are all pure meta. The tools they require are content-transverse and have no place in the content layer.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://fasparo.com/blog/antisocial-button</guid>
      <dc:date>2015-06-27T00:00:00+02:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dark modernity</title>
      <link>http://fasparo.com/blog/dark-modernity</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There is something strangely revolting about the case of Dzhokhar Tsarnaev.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2015 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://fasparo.com/blog/dark-modernity</guid>
      <dc:date>2015-05-16T00:00:00+02:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Race misunderstanding</title>
      <link>http://fasparo.com/blog/race-misunderstanding</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The competitive connotations of &amp;quot;race&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;survival of the fittest&amp;quot; are nothing but a double linguistic misunderstanding.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://fasparo.com/blog/race-misunderstanding</guid>
      <dc:date>2015-04-12T00:00:00+02:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Without religion</title>
      <link>http://fasparo.com/blog/without-religion</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Two steps forward, one step back. To all those non-believers who sigh that religion &amp;quot;is a part of human nature&amp;quot;, just look at the figures. There have never been more atheists and agnostics in the world. Humanity is freeing itself from religion just as John Lennon imagined. One day most people will think for themselves, not as tools of gods but as human beings. They will look in wonder at the universe without resort to infantilising fairy tales, without absurd supernational justifications which leave them vulnerable to manipulation by extremists. It will happen, one day.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://fasparo.com/blog/without-religion</guid>
      <dc:date>2015-03-23T00:00:00+01:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <dc:date>2015-12-19T00:00:00+01:00</dc:date>
  </channel>
</rss>