<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd"
  xmlns:trackback="http://madskills.com/public/xml/rss/module/trackback/">
  <channel>
    <title>Frepvisk</title>
    <link>http://frepvisk.com</link>
    <description>Frepvisk</description>
    <copyright>Frepvisk</copyright>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Meat hypocrite</title>
      <link>http://frepvisk.com/blog/meat-hypocrite</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Factory farming is the cruel industrial revolution of the last half-century, I&amp;#39;ve discovered from Jonathan Safran Foer&amp;#39;s Eating Animals (2008). Over 99% of all farming in the rich world has, quite suddenly, become industrial. House prices and car prices have increased 14 or 15 times, but chicken prices have barely doubled. We now eat cheaply what we most want to eat: meat.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://frepvisk.com/blog/meat-hypocrite</guid>
      <dc:date>2014-12-30T00:00:00+01:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proxy religion</title>
      <link>http://frepvisk.com/blog/proxy-religion</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Economic growth is the closest thing there is to a global religion. Rich and poor, left and right, Christians and Muslims and Buddhists and sub-Saharan animist pagans – everyone except a handful of greens is certain that growth is the answer to life, universal prosperity and almost everything else. Because government investment. Because consumer buying power. And above all because jobs.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://frepvisk.com/blog/proxy-religion</guid>
      <dc:date>2014-12-10T00:00:00+01:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Word order podium</title>
      <link>http://frepvisk.com/blog/word-order-podium</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In German, auxiliary verbs come at the end of the sentence. In the phrase, &amp;quot;I have baked a Black Forest gateau with an iced strawberry meringue topping&amp;quot;, we hear all about the cake before finding out what the speaker actually did with it. That seems illogical.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://frepvisk.com/blog/word-order-podium</guid>
      <dc:date>2014-11-29T00:00:00+01:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The meaning of streaming</title>
      <link>http://frepvisk.com/blog/meaning-streaming</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;At first sight, Spotify seems an abomination to anyone who cares about freedom online. Your music is locked down by DRM, you lose access to it if you stop paying, and Big Record Industry is monitoring what you listen to and when. But look a bit closer and things become less clear.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://frepvisk.com/blog/meaning-streaming</guid>
      <dc:date>2014-10-21T00:00:00+02:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paying for news online</title>
      <link>http://frepvisk.com/blog/reader-philanthropy</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;News organisations are tying themselves in knots over the question of how to charge users for content. Should it be per-article or subscription? Should the recent stuff be free, or the archives? And then there are apps, superfluously and expensively balkanised into multiple platforms, but which can at least be sold in virtual stores like the paper of yore. Even today, uninformed journalists are persuading themselves the future is rosy because of apps – the same journalists who have never themselves bought an app or indeed paid for any digital content. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://frepvisk.com/blog/reader-philanthropy</guid>
      <dc:date>2014-09-08T00:00:00+02:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twitter endgame</title>
      <link>http://frepvisk.com/blog/twitter-endgame</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Microblogging was invented by Twitter and for this the company deserves some success. Besides, any company endorsed by A-list celebrities and heads of state seems to me a good medium-term investment bet.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://frepvisk.com/blog/twitter-endgame</guid>
      <dc:date>2014-08-30T00:00:00+02:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neither public nor private</title>
      <link>http://frepvisk.com/blog/public-private</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;By now everyone accepts that if you post to a blog or Twitter, your thoughts are public, forever. Likewise, we all agree that it would be Completely Unacceptable for a webmail provider to leak your email to anyone at all, let alone the general public.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://frepvisk.com/blog/public-private</guid>
      <dc:date>2014-07-15T00:00:00+02:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An unsustainable contradiction</title>
      <link>http://frepvisk.com/blog/unsustainable-contradiction</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;People who are concerned about debt seem rarely to worry about growth, and vice-versa.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://frepvisk.com/blog/unsustainable-contradiction</guid>
      <dc:date>2014-06-24T00:00:00+02:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The phonetic gap</title>
      <link>http://frepvisk.com/blog/phonetic-gap</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If you were to read this sentence aloud, would listeners hear the difference between the brackets (also called parentheses) and the dashes – sometimes confused with hyphens – and if not, then why are both used?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://frepvisk.com/blog/phonetic-gap</guid>
      <dc:date>2014-05-28T00:00:00+02:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Political consumption</title>
      <link>http://frepvisk.com/blog/political-consumption</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Humanity needs to consume less. Less energy, and less stuff.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://frepvisk.com/blog/political-consumption</guid>
      <dc:date>2014-04-29T00:00:00+02:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <dc:date>2014-12-30T00:00:00+01:00</dc:date>
  </channel>
</rss>